[音乐]
[MUSIC]
凯尔：是的。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我没有
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I don't
但感觉这是正确的行为。
feel like that this is the correct behavior though.
因为当你点击一个按钮时，你会认为它会马上发生。
Cuz when you when click on a button, you would think it would happen right away.
然后当你点击
And then as you're clicking
它会再减掉整整一秒钟。&gt；&gt；Kyle：去弹跳是
it would debounce a whole nother second. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Debouncing is
不同于采样。
different than sampling.
所以我们可以做一个去弹跳的练习。
So we could have done an exercise for debouncing.
&GT；&GT；扬声器2：因为这就像，不，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Cuz this is like, no,
据我所知，这是按照练习中的模式进行的。
I understand this follows the pattern in the exercise.
但我只是说在这种情况下你有每一秒
But I'm just saying in this scenario, you have every second,
它在抛弃它看到的任何东西。
it's dumping whatever it sees.
凯尔：是的。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：对吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yes. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Right?
凯尔：是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yes.
&GT；&GT；扬声器2：我的意思是一种时钟，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I mean kind of a clock,
对吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle：是的。
right? &gt;&gt; Kyle: Yes.
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：但是我希望当
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: But I would expect that when
你点击它就可以马上操作了。
you click it just operates right away.
然后它有点-&gt；&gt；Kyle：是的。
And then it sort of- &gt;&gt; Kyle: Yeah.
所以你真正问的是什么都与你无关
So what you're really asking about has absolutely nothing to do
和程序一起。
with the programming.
这是一个用户体验问题。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
That's a user experience question. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：如果您想要用户体验
&gt;&gt; Kyle: If you wanted the user experience
去反弹，你会用不同的方法解决这个问题。
of debouncing, you would solve this a different way.
我之所以设置它，是因为采样比去抖动更容易理解。
I set it up because sampling is easier to understand than debouncing.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的，当然。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, yeah, sure.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以我设置了这个练习
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So I set it up that the exercise
就是让你学习采样。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我只是
is for you to learn about sampling. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I'm just
想知道这将如何适合-&gt；&gt；Kyle：采样适合哪里？
wondering how that would fit into the- &gt;&gt; Kyle: Where does sampling fit in?
这就是你要问的吗？&GT；&GT；扬声器2：是的，你会怎么做
Is that what you're asking? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, just how you would do
就像你用变量去抖的地方一样
it like that where you're debouncing with the variables
而不是，或者可能是[CROSSTALK]&gt；&gt；Kyle：很难回答用户
rather than, or maybe it's [CROSSTALK] &gt;&gt; Kyle: It's hard to answer user
在软件开发的上下文中体验问题。
experience questions in the context of software development.
但是有采样的用例和事件去抖的用例。
But there are use cases for sampling and there are use cases for event debouncing.
如果我们的用例要求，我们会以不同的方式解决这个问题
And we would have solved this differently if our use case was asking for
去弹跳。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：当然。
the debouncing. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Sure.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：顺便说一下，RxJS，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: And RxJS, by the way,
是否提供去抖动[CROSSTALK]&gt；&gt；扬声器2：我只是还没有完全包装
does provide a debouncing [CROSSTALK] &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I just haven't quite wrapped
我的脑袋是这样建造UI的。&gt；&gt；Kyle：有
my head around building UIs this way. &gt;&gt; Kyle: That have
取样？
sampling?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。凯尔：好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Okay.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：有流，所以我从来没有
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: With stream, so I've never
实际上构建了一个完整的反应式界面。&GT；&GT；Kyle：是的，基本上，
actually built a whole Reactive interface. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Yeah, well basically,
就像任何软件开发一样，您将拥有一组用户
just as with any software development, you're going to have a set of user
经验要求和UI要求交给你。
experience requirements and UI requirements handed to you.
作为一名开发人员，你必须说，他们的要求是什么
And as a developer you're gonna have to say, what they're asking for
是去反弹跳。
is debouncing.
所以，让我去找适当的方法来建模去抖。
So let me go find the appropriate way to model debouncing.
或者，在这里他们要求取样，
Or, over here they're asking for sampling,
让我去用一个取样的东西来解决这个问题。
let me go solve this with a sampling thing.
所以这个练习纯粹是为了解决
So this exercise was purely about solving
抽样作为我们寻找的操作。
sampling as the operation that we look for.
采样是你在接口中做的一件有效的事情。
And sampling is a valid thing that you do in interfaces.
去弹跳也是你做的一件有效的事情。
Debouncing is also a valid thing that you do.
这有道理吗？
Does that makes sense?
好吧。&gt；&gt；扬声器3：你就不能换一下吗
Okay. &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Couldn't you just switch
代替在点击时设置最新变量，
instead of having that latest variable set on click,
你会把它设置在它设定的间隔上，对吗？
you would have it set on it's set interval, r1ight?
所以它是第二个被标记的。
So that it's the second that is getting flagged.
然后每次你有点击发生，
And then every time you have the click happen,
你看，我们有第二个标志集吗？
you look to see, do we have a second flag set?
那就马上把它灭了。
Then put it out right away.
这只是不同顺序的事件
It would just be the event in the different order for
正在设置的标志。&GT；&GT；Kyle：我不会和你争论。
the flag being set. &gt;&gt; Kyle: I'm not gonna argue with you.
我不能完全肯定我是否同意，但我不会和你争论。
I'm not entirely certain I agree, but I'm not gonna argue with you.
它可能意味着[INAUDIBLE]&gt；&gt；扬声器3：您可以
It might mean [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You could
将此逻辑切换为。凯尔：好的，当然。
switch this logic around to. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Okay, sure.
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：你可以让它工作。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: You could get it working.
凯尔：好的，当然。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Okay, sure.
也许你应该这么做作为奖励。
Maybe you should do that as a bonus.
尝试将其返工为去抖动而不是采样。
Try to rework this as debouncing instead of sampling.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：嗯，我将不得不
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Well, I'm going to have to
因为我正在构建的下一个界面-
cuz one of the next interfaces I'm building-
&GT；&GT；Kyle：会是这样的，是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Is going to be that, yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：是的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Yeah.
凯尔：好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Okay.
好吧，问得好。
All right, good questions, though.
关于练习八还有其他问题吗？&gt；&gt；Kyle：这还远远不够
Any other questions about exercise eight? &gt;&gt; Kyle: This is nowhere near
一个全面的，为期两天的，深入探讨所有反应式编程的课程。
a comprehensive, two-day, deep dive into all of Reactive programming.
还有一个完全不同的车间。
There's a whole other workshop for that.
但我想让你明白的是
But what I wanted to get you to the point of is understanding where it
符合我们在项目中所做的更大范围。
fits within the bigger scope of what we do in our programs.
可观察对象是关于调整您的事件流和
Observables are about adapting your event streams and
以声明性方式对数据流进行建模。
modeling your data flow in a declarative fashion.
这就是观测值的意义所在。
That's what observables are all about.
因此，在应用程序中需要它的部分，不要使用生成器，
So in the parts of your application that need that, don't reach for a generator,
不要伸手去争取承诺，不要伸手去敲击，不要伸手去争取回电，
don't reach for a promise, don't reach for a thunk, don't reach for a callback,
伸手去找可观察到的东西。
reach for an observable.
对，所以这些都是适合的不同工具
Right, so these are all different tools that fit in
对于一个应用程序，我在研讨会开始时说了这句话。
together to an application I said this at the beginning of the workshop.
我从来没有构建过使用完全相同的抽象的应用程序
I've never once built an application that used exactly the same abstraction
遍及一切。
across everything.
有适合正确工作的工具，因此这只是您的工具中的另一个工具
There's the right tool for the right job so this is just one more tool in your tool
腰带。凯尔：你有问题吗？
belt. &gt;&gt; Kyle: Did you have a question?
好吧。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：[听不见]
Okay. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: [INAUDIBLE]
凯尔：没问题。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: No problem.
好的很好。
Okay, great.
我想指出另一件事。
I want to point out one other thing.
有几个问题是关于使用这个和
There were a couple questions about the difference between using this and
使用RxJS。
using RxJS.
我没有以任何方式贬低RxJS的形状或形式。
I'm not disparaging RxJS in any way shape or form.
我只是说，这对我来说太难了，我从来没有试过要咬掉它。
I'm simply saying it's too much for me to have ever tried to bite off.
最后，我觉得我需要更简单的东西。
And eventually, I was like I need something simpler.
所以这就是为什么它最终以不同步的方式降落。
So that's why it ended up landing in asynquence that way.
我需要一些更容易教的东西。
I needed something that was easier to teach.
如果我要教你三个或者
And if I had to teach you three or
四个不同的框架，你会比现在更加不知所措。
four different frameworks, you'd be even more overwhelmed than you are already are.
所以，我尽量让它尽可能简单。
So, I'm trying to keep it as simple as possible.
但这并不是说RxJS在任何方式，形状或形式上都是不好的，
But that's not to say in any way, shape, or form that RxJS is bad,
这是个很棒的图书馆。
it's a great library.
除此之外，我想说你不必在两者之间做出选择。
In addition to that, I would say you don't have to choose between the two,.
因为我的库中提供了一个To Observable和一个From Observable。
Because there is a to observable and a from observable provided with my library.
所以如果你有RxJS观测值，你可以从一些框架中得到。
So if you have RxJS observables that you're getting from some framework.
如果要在异步中使用它们，可以将它们导入和
And you want to use them in asynquence, you can import them in and
做一个反应序列，或者反过来。
make a reactive sequence, or the other way around.
如果你有一个反应序列，你想让一个真正可观察到的
If you have a reactive sequence and you want to make a real observable out of
因为某些原因，你也可以这样做。
it for some reason, you can do that as well.
所以你不必选择，承诺也是如此。
So you don't have to choose, and the same is true of promises.
有一种承诺和一种将承诺转化为反应的承诺方法。
There's a to promise and a promise method to bring promises into React.
所以没有真正的理由你必须画一些分界线然后说好的，
So there's no real reason why you have to draw some dividing line and say well,
不是不同步就是不同步。
it's either asynquence or not.
您可以在任何其他混合环境中混合异步
You can mix asynquence in with any other mixed environment and
应该能够透明地来回。
should be able to go back and forth transparently.